Hey.
The victims say the thieves
left them terrified for their lives.
This is the third raid on a luxury yacht
in this region in the past three weeks.
Aah! Aah!
They're amazing.
Just looks like another heap of earth to me.
Warren, may I?
Of course.
Stanley.
Hey, Stanley.
You got something?
I don't know.
Papa!
Aah!
You're an asshole.
Yes, sir.
Captain, your commander assured me that these men were professionals.
Do you think maybe you could keep them on a tighter leash?
Sergeant Ular's one of my best men.
He did not mean any harm.
We're here to explore, not to violate.
-Sergeant?     -Yes, sir.
-No more jokes.     -Yes.
It won't happen again.
Good.
Just make sure it doesn't.
So, should we take a look?
Yes.
You coming?
Um, no, you go.
Have fun.
Pryce.
We can't stay long.
If you want to hit those coordinates you gave me before...
We'll take as long as we need, Captain.
Look at him, our fearless leader.
How long have you worked for him?
I don't. Well, not directly.
Been out in the Manila Division the past four years,
keeping my head down, minding my own business.
I just got the call last week.
Drop everything, the CΕO's son needs an engineer.
So here I am, by appointment to the prince.
So that's your new boyfriend, Ario?
Piss off, Djoko.
Sorry.
What's he looking for out here?
You got any idea?
No.
Well, what do you think?
The fountain of youth?
The lost world?
Valley of Gwangi?
You're not even curious?
I'm not here to ask questions.
No, I guess not.
Me, every time I start a newjob, I like to know the basics.
You know, what are the hours and is the pay any good?
Is anyone going to be trying to shoot my head off?
You've seen something?
No, nothing solid.
Just got a feeling.
A lot of pirate activity around these islands, you know.
Mostly small-scale stuff from what I've heard, but...
It's nothing we can't handle.
No, I'm sure.
So, this your regular kind of detail?
No.
This is more like, what's it called, penance?
Last mission went bad.
We lost a man.
I'm sorry.
For what it's worth, I know how you feel.
I did eight years British Army, last four in Afghanistan,
saw a lot of men die.
Wish I could tell you it gets easier.
I'm not planning on losing any more.
Well?
We're close.
There.
What are we looking at?
Dead mine.
Colonial, probably Dutch.
They're all over these islands,
abandoned when the Japanese occupied in '42.
Εxcept this one...
This one was repurposed.
Repurposed? How?
When the Japanese invaded, they took some of these mines
and reinforced them to use as military bunkers.
So this is what we've come to find?
This is it.
Is it safe to go in?
If you're not worried about a couple of hundred tons of hillside
coming down on top of you.
There are signs of recent seismic activity.
I need to check it out.
The whole place could be unstable.
How long?
To do a thorough job, a couple of hours at least.
Well, what are you waiting for then?
Get started.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
How did you get hooked up with a guy like Pryce?
I mean, him, I get.
He's out here on some Boy's Own adventure.
Thinks he's Allan bloody Quartermain.
But you, you seem smart, serious.
This isn't just a holiday for you.
I came here for my own research.
What kind of research?
This time in our history,
the Second World War,
it's very complex.
There are still many questions.
I want to know how those men could do the things they did.
What was inside their heads.
You want to know how a soldier thinks?
Well, that's easy enough.
The way you make a soldier is you take a human being
and you reengineer him.
You break him down to the essence of what he's made of,
and then you build him back up again,
except this time,
you leave something different at the heart of him.
Duty, obedience,
whatever you want to call it.
It's something that tells him that it's okay to kill a man.
More than okay, it's his purpose.
You take a man, and you turn him into a weapon.
That's what a soldier is.
He's not just a man anymore.
He's a weapon waiting to be fired.
And you?
You were one of these weapons?
Once upon a time, yeah.
Now, not so much.
You think all soldiers are the same?
I don't know.
I haven't met them all yet.
Old movie.
You like history?
Yeah, sure.
Κeep within the perimeter.
We don't know what's out there.
He thinks I'm an idiot.
Don't worry about what he thinks.
You're the one with the money.
-You're in charge.     -Yeah, I know. I'm just...
This waiting around, it's killing me.
It won't be long now.
What was that?
Uh, I think I've been stung.
Aah!
Get down!
Get down on the ground!
Pryce!
Hyah!
Captain, take cover!
Shit.
Yah!
Get in fast!
Get out of the way!
Fall back! Fall back!
Aah!
Into the mine!
Get into the mine!
Run!
Go! Go! Come on, Go!
Run! Run!
Get in fast! Get in!
Hey, Ario!
Hey, you okay?
I think so.
Stanley, quickly!
Okay, over here.
Hey, some help here!
Pull. One, two, three!
My leg! Aah aah aah!
Aah!
Just hold your breath.
Is he gonna be okay?
Yeah, he'll be fine.
Can you give me a hand?
Captain, you got a minute?
Captain.
What's the situation?
We're not getting back out this way.
Any other options?
Well, we could try moving deeper inside and hope there's another way out.
Is it safe?
Your guess is as good as mine.
We still got communications?
Fuck.
Shit.
Who were they out there, pirates?
I don't know, maybe.
Εither that, or they could be here looking
for whatever it is he's looking for.
No.
No!
Look, whoever's out there,
there's no way they could know about this place.
-You are sure about that?     -I'm positive.
We've been very careful.
Well, I don't think there's anyone around now to listen in,
so do you think it might be time
to let the rest of us in on the big secret?
What are we looking for? What's down here?
About a year ago, one of Pricore's exploration teams
discovered an Imperial Army bunker on an island near Sumatra,
and in that bunker, there were a collection of papers.
Movement orders, delivery schedules, all written down in code.
We've been working with Rie to decode those papers...
and it was her findings that led us here.
So what's here?
During the war, General Yamashita of the Japanese army
ordered his troops to loot treasure from all over Southeast Asia.
Oh, shit, no.
For many years, it was believed
the treasure was buried somewhere in the Philippines.
This is a treasure hunt?
Yamashita's gold. It's a myth, an old wives' tale.
-It doesn't exist.     -Not in the Philippines, no.
You think it's here?
Well, the code identifies a number of locations,
including this island, with a symbol for gold.
It's bullshit.
For fuck's sake.
Is that what all this is for?
You don't like gold, Mr. Stanley?
I'd rather be poor and alive.
So how many people know about this?
About the location of this mine and the gold?
It's the just the people on this mission.
It's just us.
You're not falling for this shit, are you?
You asked me why we're here, and I just told you!
Now, you don't have to believe me if you don't want to.
Oh, don't fucking worry.
But the fact is, we could be a few feet away
from the biggest haul of treasure in living memory.
Or we could be walking into a fucking death trap.
You know what?
It does not matter what we believe.
Gold or no gold,
we've still got to find another way out of here.
I suggest we start moving.
Hold it.
Stanley.
How does it look?
Quiet as a grave, and about as welcoming.
Still, you know what they say,
when you're going through hell, keep going.
Hmm.
Fuck.
What's it saying?
It's a war song. Propaganda.
"Wipe out Americans and Britons."
Say anything about Indonesian?
There's someone in here?
Could it be a result of the mine damage?
Maybe it triggered a generator or something.
After all this time?
Jeez, I don't know.
But how could someone be in here?
That entrance hadn't been uncovered in decades.
There must be another way in, which is good for us,
'cause it means there's another way out of here.
Who is it?
It's probably the same bastards who were trying to shoot us.
They know we're in here.
They're just making sure we know they're here.
Keep your eyes open, watch your step.
Let's move.
Ohh.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Clear.
What's the matter?
Didn't they leave a treasure map?
Come on, we should keep moving.
You getting what you came for?
Yes, thank you.
Clear.
Communications center.
These are Imperial Army positions from 1945,
and this is us.
The markings for this bunker refer to the 25th Area Army.
Yamashita.
You still think there's gold down here, Pryce?
All the signs point to it, yeah.
-And what else?     -I'm sorry?
There's something you're not telling us.
Something about this place doesn't feel right.
This isn't just a standard bunker,
and it's not a bank vault, either.
And those photos you found, they weren't just personnel files.
They were medical.
So what was this place, some kind of hospital?
No, not a hospital.
-Rie, wait.     -No!
They need to know everything.
Okay.
According to our information,
this bunker was an operating center for a satellite division of Unit 731.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
Unit 731 was a secret medical research unit.
It specialized in the development of biological and chemical warfare
through the means of lethal human experimentation.
Wow, this just gets better.
What we talking, nerve gas, germ warfare?
That kind of thing, yes.
You did nothing to tell us this.
What does it matter?
You're here to do your job.
You're soldiers.
Soldiers, not guinea pigs.
You should have told us.
You should have let us get prepared.
I wasn't planning to get trapped in here!
I thought there'd be more time.
Listen, whatever's in here,
it's been locked away for nearly 70 years.
-If we're careful...     -It's not just up to us though, is it?
There's someone else in here.
So what about the gold then?
If the gold's really here...
why would they need it?
We don't know.
The records we have are incomplete.
Maybe they used Unit, what is that, 731,
as a cover story
to keep everyone away.
Yeah, that's right.
You get everyone scared of what's down here
so they don't come looking.
Unless they're too fucking stupid to stay away.
Don't pretend you'd have done anything different.
A man like you turning down the money I'm offering.
A man like me?
Hey, hey, cool it!
You cool it.
I'm cool.
Any more surprises?
No.
Good.
All clear.
All of you wait here.
Keep clear of the entrance.
Djoko will cover.
Wait a minute, where do you think you're going?
To look for another way out.
We'll move quicker if there's just the two of us.
No, no, no, that's not how this works.
I'm paying for this mission.
I don't care about your money,
and I don't care about your gold.
All I care about is getting us out of here alive.
And I've come too far and gambled too much
to let someone else be the one who finds the gold.
No.
We're coming with you, Captain, whether you like it or not.
You want to get yourself killed?
It's up to you.
Rie?
No.
I'm sorry?
I'll wait here for now.
You sure? We could use you.
We'll be fine.
Come on.
Let's go.
Captain,
you need me?
No.
Jesus, break it to me gently.
Remember how to use one of these?
I'll get by.
Thanks.
Take care of him.
Of course.
Thank you.
Clear.
So, why did you give it up?
What, the Army?
Now, there's a question.
You really want to know?
Last time back from Afghanistan, I had a night out,
just a few of the lads, local pub, nothing to it.
This guy bumps into me on the way to the bar...
doesn't say sorry.
So I say a few words, he calls me a few names,
and the next thing I know,
I smashed a bottle over his head.
So he's lying there on the ground,
bleeding into the carpet,
and I'm looking at him,
and it's all I can do to stop myself taking the broken bottle
and just opening up this throat.
It's like second nature, instinct.
It's all that makes sense.
Just finish it, kill him.
I didn't do it, of course.
I got pulled away, bundled into the back of a taxi
before the police came.
But that's when I got scared,
thinking how close I came.
And it wasn't about the killing.
That wasn't what bothered me.
What bothered me...
was liking it.
What is it?
Australian issue.
Allied troops.
Prisoners of war.
For their experiments.
We don't know that.
This Unit 731...
that's why you're here, isn't it?
Yes.
You should have told us from the start.
Would it have made any difference to you?
Probably not,
but don't tell Pryce that.
Aah!
Ario!
What the fuck was that?
What the fuck was that?!
Ario!
Tell me what's in there. You tell me what's in there!
I don't know! I swear!
Wait!
Ario!
Shit.
-Wait here.     -No, I'm coming with you!
Have you got a weapon? Training?
Do you even know what we're up against?
Do you?
Take this.
And stay close.
Ario!
Shh.
What are you doing?
Rie.
No.
He's gone.
I know it's hard, I know that,
but we can't stay here.
We've got to move, okay?
Okay?
Good.
Stanley!
Stay close.
Be careful in here.
What are they?
Medical notes,
formulas...
research for their experiments.
Hmm! Sick bastards.
Ario.
Aah!
Ario!
What the fuck?
Aah!
Aah! Fuck!
Unh!
Ah!
Ah aah!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Djoko.
What's happening?
We're locked in.
Damn.
He wants you to know that you are now a prisoner
of the Japanese Imperial Army.
What is this? What's happening.
He thinks... He thinks we're the enemy, the Allies.
The Allies?
I told him that the war is over.
He doesn't want to believe me.
He thinks I'm a traitor.
You want to try telling him again?
Aah!
No!
Keep working.
This is fucking crazy.
You're telling me he's been here for 70 fucking years?
What did he say?
"Never surrender."
Hey, careful.
What are you doing?
He needs to see.
What you showing him?
Archive.
Footage from the final Japanese surrender in 1945.
Well, do you think that will work?
I don't know.
What's he saying?
He said Tadaki was right.
Who's Tadaki?
Aah!
Pryce!
Su-Ling.
All right.
Aah!
Pryce.
Your jacket, quickly!
Okay, press. Press.
Press hard.
It'll be okay.
Miss Ling.
Miss Ling!
We got to keep it together, okay?
He says that he's been guarding this place for years.
When the Japanese Army left in 1945,
he was sealed in.
There were two of them.
What happened to the other one?
When the radio broke down,
Tadaki wanted to leave, to surrender.
He believed the reports, but I didn't believe him.
We fought, and I...
I killed him.
So if he's the last of the guards,
what was that thing that took the soldier?
There were others here before us.
Prisoners.
They made them into monsters.
Pryce.
He can't hurt you. He's dead.
Warren.
I'm okay.
You read Japanese?
Yeah.
What's that say?
It says "Australian, 24 years."
He's a POW.
After all this time.
How?
I... I don't know.
Maybe that's what all this was about.
To turn the enemy into guard dogs.
Do you think this thing is a weapon?
I don't know what to think.
We should expect more company.
They experimented on the prisoners.
The gas drove them mad, transformed them,
made them into beasts.
Then they discovered a new process.
They gave us injections,
told us it would keep us young, keep us strong.
But it was just another experiment,
another failure.
What's it all for?
What were they trying to do here?
They were trying to make human weapons,
impossible soldiers.
And this is what they got?
What's he saying?
He says that they were not the last of the experiments.
They perfected the formula.
Gave it to their best.
The Imperial Guard.
Papa.
Oh, God.
Jesus.
What is it?
It's gold.
It's what they've been using for the experiments.
That's the secret.
That's what they've been hiding here.
No, that can't be it.
That can't be it!
So this is what you've been looking for, hmm?
This is Yamashita's gold?
We need to get out of here and find the others.
How the hell did we get in here?
Oh, here.
Ask him if there's another way out of the bunker.
He says there is tunnels to the surface.
From here?
No. He'll have to show us.
You trust him?
No.
But he knows what's out there,
and he's stayed alive this long.
Okay, but let's keep an eye on him, yeah?
I don't think the war's over for him yet.
Why gold?
It's the ancient elixir of life,
the basis of alchemy.
They must have found a way to use it,
a way to make those things out there.
That's why the gold was here.
Fuck.
There must be more than this.
I can't go back with nothing.
You won't.
If this is what they gave them,
if this is what turned human beings
into whatever it is out there,
then this could be worth more than the gold ever was.
Put this somewhere safe.
Okay.
Hey, you two,
wait here.
Hold it there!
Get out of here!
-In there!     -Aah!
-Move!     -Aah!
Help me!
Aah!
Go! Go!
Wait, where are you going?
You can't leave us!
No!
Shh.
Ah!
-No, quiet.     -Look, I can't help it.
All right, let's go.
Oh!
Okay, go back.
Get back!
Aah!
Help!
Aah! Aah!
Come on!
Help him! Help him!
Ah!
Aah!
Go!
Jesus.
You ought to wave a flag or something next time.
-Any sign?     -No.
What about the rest of your men?
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your fault, none of this.
I brought them here.
They were soldiers. They knew the score.
No, not this time.
None of us did.
Does he know a way out of here?
He reckons there's a tunnel underneath the holding cells.
It's how the POWs get out to find food, hunting animals.
Well, that's down at the lab.
That's where we just came from.
I know.
You trust him?
We don't have a choice.
Okay.
Let's move.
Wait, he's in a very bad way.
It can't be helped.
He didn't know about any of this.
He knew more than I did,
more than any of us.
Shh shh.
What did you do?!
Are you mad?
It's kept those things alive, why not him?
-Warren! Warren!     -Pryce!
Aah!
Come on! Move!
Rie, come on!
Ah!
No.
-Where is she?     -I don't know. I'll go back.
Aah!
Unh!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Rie.
-Unh!     -Rie.
No, don't!
Open the door!
Look, we can't stay here.
We've got to move.
Come on!
Damn it, you have to help me!
Lord.
Come on, Warren!
No!
No, not that way. That way!
Go!
Help me!
Come on!
Stanley!
The drain system!
Get it open!
Hurry!
We can't hold them back for much longer!
It's open!
Go!
Do I need to make that an order?
No. You don't have to do this.
Go now!
Aah!
Warren.
Warren, you need to get up.
You need to get up and move just a few more feet.
We're nearly there.
I've seen it, Warren, just a few more feet!
Warren!
Warren?
Aah!
Stanley?
Just keep going.
We've got no choice.
Stanley!
Aah!
嘿！
受害者说抢劫犯扔下他们
还恐吓说要他们的命
在过去的三周里，这是该地区发生的
第三起豪华游轮抢劫案了
啊！啊…
死亡矿坑
他们太让人震撼了
我怎么看都是一堆土
沃伦，我可以看看吗？
当然
斯坦利
嘿，斯坦利
你发现什么了？
我也说不好
爸爸！
啊！
你个混蛋！
安全，长官
长官，你的指挥员向我打包票说这些人可都是受过专业训练的
你能管好他们吗？
尤尔军士是我最得力的手下之一
他并没有恶意
我们来这儿是探险的，不是冒犯他人的
-是的  -长官
-别再开玩笑了  -是
不会再有类似情况了
很好
保证不会有下次了
那，我们进去看看？
好
你要一起过来不？
呃，不了，你们去吧
旅途偷快
普耐斯
我们不能长待
你要是想确定那些坐标，你先给我…
我们任务完成就回来，长官
看看他，我们畏手畏脚的头儿
你帮他打工多久了？
我不帮他打工好吧，不是直接的
我在马尼拉区待了四年
夹着尾巴，兢兢业业工作
就在上周接到了这个电话
我就放下了一切，只因总裁的儿子需要一个工程师
然后我就来了，陪这位公子哥儿
阿瑶，那是你的新男友？
狄吉欧，你滚开
不好意思
他在那儿找什么？
你知道不？
不知道
那你觉得呢？
青春之泉？
遗失的大陆？
迷失的山谷？
你就不好奇？
我来这儿不是问问题的
我想也不是
而我，每次接到新任务，总会搞清楚大致方向在哪儿
比如说，截止日期是什么时候啊，我能得到什么好处啊
会不会有人正准备打爆我的头？
你看见什么了？
没有具体看见什么
就是有一种不好的感觉
你知道，这些岛上有很多秘密活动的
我听到了一些细细碎碎的声音，但是…
没有我们处理不了的问题
是的，这点我深信不疑
那么，你们平时就干这种工作？
不是
这次任务，准确的说，更像是一次惩罚
上个任务，我们搞砸了
我们失去了一员
我很抱歉
我知道你的感觉
我在英国军队服役八年，最后四年在阿富汗
亲眼见到很多人死去
一切都会好起来的
我不会再让我的任何一名手下牺牲了
怎么样？
快了
看那儿
我们在找什么？
死亡矿坑
这些殖民矿坑，估计是荷兰的
它们遍布这些岛屿
日本1942年占领这儿以后，这些矿坑就废弃了
除了这座…
这座被重新利用了
重新利用？干吗？
日本入侵以后，他们占领了这些矿坑
并把其改造成了军事堡垒
那这就是我要找的？
正是
可以进去吗？
只要你不怕山体滑坡
数百吨石头向你砸来
有近期地震活动的迹象
我得查看一下
整个区域可能不稳定
得多久？
整体查下来，至少得几个小时
那你还等什么？
开始吧
能问你个问题吗
说吧
你为什么和普耐斯这样一个人共事？
我是说，据我所知
他来这儿纯粹是男生式的探险
以为自己是《所罗门宝藏》的男主角
但你，看起来如此漂亮，端庄
对你来说，这次探险不会向假期那么轻松的
我来这儿是为了自己的研究
什么研究？
我们的历史
二战
是很复杂的
还有很多未解之谜
我想知道那些人是怎样做到过去他们做的那些事的
他们是怎么想的
你想知道一个士兵是怎么想的？
好吧，这就容易了
就把他们当普通人看
再重新构造下
你想像下，把他拆分成每个人都有的原始构造
然后再重新组合
但是这次
在他心里放些与众不同的东西
比如说，责任，服从
随便你怎么称呼这些特点吧
就是这些东西告诉他们杀人没什么大不了的
还不是没什么大不了的，杀人就是他们的目的
你训练一个人，变成一件武器
这就是士兵
他就不再是一个人了
而是一件武器，等着开火
那你呢？
你也曾是这些武器之一吗？
对，曾经
现在不是了
你觉得所有士兵都是那样的吗？
我不知道
我没有见过所有的士兵
老电影了
你喜欢历史？
当然
大家都待在附近
我们不知道外面有什么
他把我当傻瓜
别在意他的想法
你是出资人
-你才是头儿  -我知道，我只是…
就这样待在这儿，对我来说是一种折磨
不会很久的
刚才是什么？
呃，我觉得被刺了一下
啊！
趴下！
都趴在地上！
普耐斯！
耶
长官，掩护！
糟糕！
呀！
快进去！
别挡道！
退后！退后！
啊！
进矿井！
快进矿井！
快跑！
快走！快走！快点，走
跑啊，跑啊！
快进去，快进去！
嘿，阿瑶！
嘿，你没事吧？
没事
斯坦利，快点！
好的，这边
嘿，过来这儿帮忙
拉，1，2，3！
我的胞！啊！
啊！
屏住呼吸
他会没事吗？
是，他会好起来的
能帮我一下吗？
长官，你能过来看下吗？
长官
怎么了？
这条路出不去了
还有其他路没？
那只能往里走，看看有其他出口没
那样安全吗？
我的想法和你一样
我们的通信还畅通么？
妈的
糟糕
谁在外面，海盗？
我不知道，也许吧
任何一个，都能到这儿
找寻他们想要的
不
不！
看，不论谁在外面
他们都不可能知道知道这个地方
-你确定么？  -我肯定
我们一直以来都很小心
好吧，我不认为现在周围有人在听
那么你觉得现在是时候
让我们知道这个大秘密了么？
我们在找寻什么？下面是什么？
大约一年前，一名布菜克勘探队的队员
在苏门答腊岛上，发现了一个帝国军队地堡
在那个地堡里，有一些纸张
移动命令，到达时间表，都是用代码写的
我一直和瑞在对那些纸张解码…
正是她的发现带我们来到了这儿
那么这儿有什么？
战争期间，日本军队的上将山下翔央
命令他的部下从东南亚的各个角落搜刮钱财
哦，呸，不会吧
多年来，都被认为
那些财宝被埋在了菲律宾的某个地方
这是一个寻宝游戏？
山下翔央的金子一个神话，一个无稽之谈
-它是不从在的  -不在菲律宾，不是的
你觉得在这儿？
好吧，密码确定一个位置的坐标
包括这个岛，有一个金子标志
胡说
我他妈求你了
这就是我们所为的一切？
你不喜欢金子，斯坦利先生？
我宁愿穷活着
那有多少人知道这个？
我们的地点和金子？
只有参加这次任务的人
只有我们
你陷入到这个鬼事情了，是么？
你问我为什么到这儿的，所以我告诉你们了
现在，如果你不想，可以不相信我
哦，别他妈的担心
但是事实上，我们只有在活的记忆中把宝藏
最多拉几英尺远
或者我们走入一个该死的死亡陷阱
你知道么？
这与我们的信仰无关
金子或者没有金子
我们都会找另外一条出去的路
我建议我们开始行动
等一下
斯坦利
这个看上去怎么了？
安静的像一座坟墓，也许是在欢迎
仍然记得他们说的
当你要穿过地狱时，持续往前走
嗯
妈的
那是什么声音？
是一个战争歌曲，宣传
“消灭美国人和英国人”
没有说任何关于印尼的么？
这里面有人么？
这是一个自我毁灭装置么？
也许它会引爆一个发电机或者什么东西
一直以来都有么？
呀，我不知道
但是这里怎么可能有人呢？
入口数十年都没开启过
一定有另外的入口，这对我们有益
“这意味着有我们有另外一条路能逃出去”
那他是谁？
也许是同样想杀我们的混蛋
他们知道我们在这里
他们只是确保我们知道他们在这儿
紧睁双眼，注意脚下
我们走
哦
嘿
你没事吧？
是的
检查过了
怎么了？
他们没留下藏宝图？
走吧，我们要继续前进
你拿到了你想要的？
是的，谢谢
已检查
通信中心
这是帝国军1945年的阵地
这是我们
这个碉堡的标记指的是第25地方军队
山下翔央
你还觉得这底下有金子，普莱斯？
所有的标记都指向它，是的
-那还有什么？  -抱歉？
有些事你没有告诉我们
这个地方的有些东西感觉不太对
这不只是一个标准的堡垒
他也不是一个银行金库
你找到的那些照片，也不是私人文件
他们是医学的
那么，这是个什么地方，什么医院？
不，不是医院
-瑞，等等  -不！
他们需要知道一切
好吧
根据我们的信息
这个碉堡是731部队的卫星操控中心
我先知道它意查味着什么？
731部队是一个秘密的医学研究部队
他们专门从事研究生化武器
通过致命的人体试验
喔，这变得更好了
我们在讨论什么？神经毒气？细菌战？
是这样的
你没有和我们说过这些
这有什么关系？
你到这儿是完成你的工作
你是军人
军人，不是试验品
你应该告诉我们
你应该让我们有所准备
我没打算被困在这儿！
我以为会有更多的时间
听着，不管这里有什么
都被关接近70年了
-如果我们小心点儿…  -但这不仅仅只关于我们，不是么？
有其他人在这里
那么黄金呢？
如果金子真的在这里…
他们为什么需要它？
我们不知道
我们所拥有的记录还不完全
也许他们用单位，什么来着，731
作为一个封面故事
让大家都远离
是的，没错
你让大家对下面的东西都产生了恐惧
所以都不来寻找
除非他们太他妈的愚蠢才呆在这儿
不要假装你想做些不同的事情
我提供一个像你一样拒绝钱的男人
一个像我这样的男人？
嘿，嘿，冷静点儿！
你冷静点
我很冷静
还有更多惊喜么？
没了
很好
已检查
你们都在这儿等着
保持入口开着
乔克会看着的
等一下，你想去干什么？
去找另一条出去的路
如果只有我们两个行动会快点儿
不，不，不，不能这样做
我为这次任务付钱
我才不关心你的钱
而且我也不关心你的金子
我只关心把我们或者弄出去
我们千里迢迢而来，孤注一掷
让其他人成为找到金子的人
不行
我们和你一起去，上尉，不论你高不高兴
你想让你自己被杀？
这由你决定
瑞？
我不去
什么？
我会在这儿等着
你确定？我们会用到你
我们挺好啊
走吧
我们走
长官
你需要我么？
不需要
天啊，温柔的伤害了我
还记得怎么用这个么？
我会用
谢谢
照顾他
当然
谢谢
检查完毕
你为什么要放弃呢？
什么，军队？
现在，有个问题
你真的想知道？
上次从阿富汗会来后，有天晚上我出去了
只有极少数的小伙子，在当地的酒吧，不要紧
这家伙在我去酒吧的路上撞到我了…
没有说抱歉
后来我说几句话，他报了几个名字
接下来发生的就是
我用了个瓶子爆了他的头
然后他就倒在地上
躺在地毯上流血
而我就看着他
只有这能不让我捡起碎瓶子
插进他的喉咙里
这就像是第二天性
这就是全部的意义
干掉他，杀了他
当然，我没那么做
我离开了，在警察到来之前
钻进一辆出租车后座
但是从那时起，我就感到害怕
想想看就差那一点点
这不是关于杀不杀的问题
这不是真正困扰我的事情
真正困扰我的
是喜欢一样东西
那是什么？
澳大利亚造的东西
同盟军
俘虏
为了他们的实验
我们还不清楚
这个731部队…
这才是你来的原因吧？
是的
你一开始就应该告诉我们的
这对于你来说有什么不同吗？
估计没有
但是普耐斯可不会这么认为
啊！
阿瑶！
那他妈的是什么东西？
那他妈的到底是个什么？
阿瑶！
告诉我那里面是什么，你告诉我
我不知道，我发誓！
等等！
阿瑶！
妈的
-在这里等着  -不，我要跟你们一起去
你有武器吗？你接受过训练吗？
你知道你面对的是个什么吗？
那你知道吗？
拿着这个
跟紧点
阿瑶！
嘘
你要干嘛？
瑞
不
他死了
我知道这很难受，我知道
但是我们不能留在这里
我们必须离开，懂吗？
懂吗？
很好
斯坦利！
靠紧点
小心这里
这是什么？
医学备注
化学方程式
他们实验的研究
嗯，一帮变态
阿瑶
啊！
阿瑶！
这他妈是什么东西？
啊！
啊！妈的！
啊！啊！
啊！
狄吉欧
怎么了？
我们被锁在里面了
他妈的
他想让你知道，你现在是
一名日本皇军的俘虏
这是什么？怎么回事？
他认为…他认为，我们是敌人，是同盟军
同盟军？
我告诉过他战争已经结束了
但是他不信
他认为我是个汉奸
你想要再告诉他一遍？
啊！
住手！
继续努力
这他妈的疯狂了
你是在说他在这里他妈的待了70年？
他说什么？
永不投降
嘿，小心点
你要干什么？
他应该看看
你在给他看什么？
档案
1945年日本最终投降的片段
那你觉得这会有用吗？
我不知道
他说什么？
他说塔达基是对的
塔达基是谁？
啊！
普耐斯！
林小姐
没事的
啊！
普耐斯！
你的外套，快！
好了，压着压着
用点劲
会没事的
林小姐
林小姐！
我们必须一起压着，好吗？
他说他很多年来一直在守护这个地方
自从日军1945年离开以后
他就被封印在这个地方
他们有两个人
另一个怎么了？
当时无线电坏了
塔达基想离开，想投降
他相信报告所说的，但是我不相信他
于是我们打起来了…
我杀了他
那如果他是最后的守护者
那又是什么东西把阿瑶拖走的？
在我们之前，这里是有人来过的
战俘
他们把他们变成了怪兽
普耐斯！
他不会伤害你的，他死了
沃伦
没事的
你认识日语？
是的
这上面写的什么？
写的是‘澳大利亚人，24年’
他是个战俘
这么长时间过去了
怎么可能？
我不知道
也许这就是传说里的东西
把敌人变成看门狗
你觉得这是个武器吗？
我不知道怎么去想
我们应该有更多的支援
他们在战俘身上做了实验
毒气把他们弄疯了，改造了他们
把他们变成野兽
后来他们发现了一种新方法
通过给他们注射
让他们保持年富力强
但这只是又一个实验
又一次失败的实验
这一切是为了什么？
他们在这里尝试着做的是什么？
他们在试着制造人体武器
无敌战士
那这就是他们得到的结果？
他说什么？
他说这不是他们的最新成果
他们改良了配方
让他们做到最好
帝国护卫
爸爸
噢，天哪
上帝啊
这是什么？
是黄金
这是他们用作试验用的
这就是秘密
这就是他们在这儿隐藏的东西
不，这不可能
不可能！
这就是你要找的东西，嗯？
美香的黄金？
我们要出去找到其他人
我们到底怎么到这儿的？
哦，从这里
问问他有没有别的路出去
他说有条通道直通地面
就从这里？
不，他说会指给我们看
你相信他吗？
不相信
但是他知道外面是什么样的
而且他活了这么长时间，一直待在这里
好吧，但是得注意着他一点儿
我可不认为他承认战争已经结束了
为什么用黄金？
古时候的炼金药‘长生不老药’
基本的炼丹术
他们一定知道怎么用这些
一种把人变成外面那些家伙的方法
这就是为什么黄金在这里
妈的
肯定还有更多的
我不能空着手回去
你不会的
如果这就是他们给他们注射的
如果这就是把人变成
外面那些东西的
那他本身的价值就远高于黄金
把它放在一个安全的地方
好的
嘿，你们两个
在这里等着
站住
快出去
-进去！  -啊！
-快快快！  -啊！
帮帮我！
啊！
快走！
等等，你去哪儿？
你不能离开我们！
不！
嘘
啊！
-别出声  -不是我能控制的好不好
好了，我们走
噢
好了，退回去
退回去
啊！
救命！
啊！啊！
快走！
拉他一把！
啊！
走！
上帝啊
你下次应该挥个小旗或者什么的
-有什么发现吗？  -没有
你的人呢？
对不起
这不是你的错，这一切都不是
是我把他们带来这里的
他们是士兵，他们知道代价的
但不是这一次
不是我们任何人的错
他知道出去的路吗？
他说在承重单元下面有个通道
那些战俘就是从那里出去觅食捕猎的
那是在实验室下面
我们就刚从那里来的
我知道
你相信他吗？
我们没得选啊
好吧
走吧
等等，他现在状态很差
那没办法
他之前也不知道会有这些啊
他比我知道多
比我们任何人知道的都多
嘘，嘘
你干了什么？
你疯了吗？
这东西能让那些怪物活着，为什么不能让他活着？
-沃伦！沃伦！  -普耐斯！
啊！
快走！快！
瑞，快跟上！
啊！
不会吧
-她去哪儿了？  -不知道，我回去找她
啊！
呀！
瑞！
-呀！  -瑞！
不要
开门
快开门
我们不能在这儿等死
赶紧离开这儿
快
妈的，你就不能帮点忙吗？
天哪
加油，沃伦！
不要！
不，不是那边，这边
快
救我
顶住
斯坦利！
排水系统！
打开它
快点！
我们坚持不了多久了
打开了！
快走
要我下命令吗？
不，你不必那么做了
快走啊
啊！
沃伦
沃伦快站起来
你只要站起来，往前挪几步就好了
我们很接近出口了
我看就了，沃伦，就几步
沃伦！
沃伦？
啊！
斯坦利？
继续前进
我们别无选择
斯坦利！
啊！
字
字幕
字幕制
字幕制作
字幕制作 ★
字幕制作 ★ 至
字幕制作 ★ 至宏
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上人